http://www.breakthroughbasketball.com/privacypolicy.html

The Internet's #1 Website for Basketball Camps, Resources and Learning Products
BreakthroughBasketball.com Privacy Policy
Our Commitment To Privacy:
Your privacy is important to us. We want you to feel comfortable using our website and know that we keep your information secure. We do NOT share your information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete your order with well known credit card processing companies.
To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and on every other page of this website.
The Personal Information We Collect:
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the BreakthroughBasketball.com website. On some pages, you can order informational products, make requests or comments, and register to receive newsletters and other materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages may include:
- Your name
- Your address
- Your email address
- Your telephone number
- Your credit card or debit card information
- Your password
- Whether you are a coach, parent or player
- What age level you coach
Other Information We Collect:
You can visit our website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself.
We track the Internet address of the domains from which people visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but the individual user remains anonymous.
We automatically log personal data via our website when you send us an electronic message, as well as log information automatically with each individual visit to our website. We save a logfile to a secure folder for internal reporting purposes. We do so for the following purposes:
-
Logfile Analysis
-
Click Stream Analysis
-
Technical Administration of the Website
-
Research and Development
-
Customer Administration
-
Marketing
Retention of Personal Information:
Your personal information will be retained for as long as it is necessary to carry out the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy (unless longer retention is required by applicable law). However, we will not retain any of your personal information beyond this period and the retention of your personal information will be subject to periodic review. We may keep an anonymized form of your personal information, which will no longer refer to you, for statistical purposes without time limits, to the extent that we have a legitimate and lawful interest in doing so.
Cookies:
When you visit our website, we may place an informational text file about you called a "cookie", in the browser files of your computer's hard drive. Generally websites use the information to improve your experience in their site. For example, a cookie allows the ability to personalize information, or to help with online sales, or simply for the purposes of tracking popular pages on a site or demographics.
Cookies also provide programmers with a quick and convenient means of keeping website content fresh and relevant to the user's interests. This information can be valuable to targeting content or advertising to you. The cookie itself does not contain personal information, although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites.
We also use cookies to track user traffic patterns.
You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use the public area of this site, however you'll need cookies enabled to access the password protected "membership area" of this site.
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete your order.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that a certain number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out.
Transfer of Information:
If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, we may transfer your information to the United States (or any other country where we operate), where the privacy laws may not be as protective as in your country or jurisdiction. By using our website, you consent to the collection, transfer, use, storage, and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.
Please be aware that information you provide to us or that we obtain as a result of your use of our services may be collected in your country and subsequently transferred to the United States or another country in accordance with applicable law. The privacy and data protection laws in the country to which your information is transferred may not be equivalent to such laws in your country of residence. Your personal information may be subject to the laws of the country to which it is transferred and may be accessible without notice to you by the courts, law enforcement and national security authorities of that country. By using our website or providing us with your information, you consent to the collection, international transfer, storage, and processing of your information.
Our Commitment To Data Security:
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:
We do not knowingly collect or store contact information about children under the age of 13 in the United States or the appropriate age for services directed toward children as defined under applicable laws in other jurisdictions.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by using this form to contact us. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
Changes to Privacy Statement:
If we decide to change our privacy statement, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it.
How to Contact Us:
If at any time, you have questions or concerns about the BreakthroughBasketball.com's privacy statement, please feel free to contact us by visiting this page.
Last Updated July 12, 2018
FIRST NAME
EMAIL
AGE LEVEL
Youth
Middle School
CATEGORY
I'm a Coach
Subscribe to our free monthly newsletter to receive new drills, plays, scoring tips and coaching strategies,
plus three free eBooks with over 270 pages of our favorite basketball drills and plays!
Please do not change the values in the following 4 fields, they are just to stop spam bots. Leave them blank if they are currently blank.
Subscribe to our free monthly newsletter to receive three free eBooks with over 270 pages of content!
Breakthrough Basketball, LLC.
Facebook (74k Likes)
YouTube (56.8k Subscribers)
Twitter (25.7k Followers)
Q&A Forum
Podcasts
© Copyright 2020 Breakthrough Basketball, LLC.
Get 3 Free eBooks Now!
Simply subscribe to our monthly newsletter and receive:
72 Basketball Drills & Coaching Tips - 136 page eBook
21 Basketball Tips & Tricks for Players - 20 page eBook
32 Winning Basketball Plays - 96 page eBook
Plus, you'll receive new drills, plays, scoring tips and coaching strategies delivered to your inbox each month.
Please do not change the values in the following 4 fields, they are just to stop spam bots. Leave them blank if they are currently blank.
Get 3 FREE eBooks Now!
Receive 72 drills, 32 plays & 7 shooting workouts!
